It has begun! Open Challenge!
This time's challenge project is
The seniority competition!
I love it!
I can't get through it.
Why?
What does it mean to "bump into your senpai"?
I love you guys!
Let's bump it!
That's right, mid-year rights.
We'll stick it to each other. We're the least sticking it to each other.
The least smug is the best!
But I bet you're both bugs!
If we don't play hard to get, we won't be able to get along with the seniors.
I know that.
That's the cause.
I think it's the cause.
But I can't.
What do you mean by "put your head in the sand"?
I mean, it's the cause.
It's the cause.
And you.
You too.
Pretty for you, I'm not saying it's a chain of events.
I'm not gonna mind
Hear me now
If it's a word, I don't need it anymore
It's up now, it's up now
You and me, so destiny
Let me explain.
I'd like to explain this project.
Today we're going to be talking with
We're going to be with Yuzuki Okura
Yuzuki Okura.
Yuzuki's character.
Thank you very much.
In the meantime, Yuzuki is working on
Amegrash's fake YouTube project
Yuzuki is going to appear on Amegrash's YouTube
Thank you very much.
You're so kind.
Yuzuki will be answering questions from Amegrash
Yuzuki will be answering questions about Amegrash.
Actually... we are...
We're going to use a pre-determined
Yuzuki-chan to answer the pre-determined words
Yuzuki-chan to answer the pre-determined questions.
Ah...
While working on his project...
Yes, that's right.
It's difficult!
If you succeed in the challenge!
There's a big prize waiting for you.
He says there's a prize waiting for you.
I'll do it.
Please let me do it.
I'll put my heart and soul into it.
Oh, no.
It's not that bad, is it?
No, it'd be bad if something weird came in.
I'm so... so... so...
I'm worried...
Stop it!
Shut up and get it over with!
You mean you're going to bump me?
I don't mean I'm going to smack you.
You mean you're gonna smack me?
Oh, my God!
First of all,
We all have to hit each other.
We all have to bash each other at least once.
I see.
Well then!
No way!
I'm going to use a sarcasm.
Calling people by their first names.
Calling people by the wrong name
Replying with a "YASUKO YES! Reply with a "Yes!
Aaaaah!
Eeeeeeeeee!
What, you mean I have to do all of these?
Someone has to do all of them.
One?
One time for sure?
I just have to say "Mr. Oshiro"?
Is that what you mean?
But if I say Mr. Oshiro...
They'll understand.
When you introduce yourself.
Mr. Oshiro, thank you for coming today.
And then you say you're Mr. Oshiro.
Then I'm in trouble.
Then I'll connect you.
And then you and Yasuko-san...
Isn't it hard to do that?
Once you know which hand is coming from Yasuko-san.Which hand moment is from Yasuko once?
Se-no!
Yes!
Oh, no, no, no, no!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good.
Peketan, please.
Peketan, can I?
Peketan, I'll win!
Peketan Pooh's Enjoy!
Now, let's continue, and then someone else will bump it up.
Oh, yes, that's right.
Well, in short, one of us has to bump it in.
Oh, I see. Sometimes I have Hannah do all the work.
That's right. No?
No, they want us to cooperate.
Then I'll make an announcement. This way.
First one. I knew you long time ago.
Oh no.
Next one is... Are you having a bad day?
Eeeee.
The last one is bad.
I can't eat at all.
The moment I started coughing a little, he said, "Are you having a bad day?
What do you do when you cough a little?
We all started a little coughing boom.
Oh, but the inner music section was a little bit broken.
Ah.
Are you very sick?
Is that bad?
It's a little bit bad, isn't it? Is it because it's the rainy season?
I'm not so sure.
I'm not eating well.
No grueling food.
Let's take your foot off the gas.
In that case, I'll just say, "What?
Today, I'm going to collaborate with you, right? Sunday.
So, I'm going to say something like, "I wish I had done that... I have to make them eat it.
I have to make them eat it.
It would be strange if I said I didn't like it.
But this would be boring if I don't do it seriously.
I want them to scream like crazy.
Oh, no.
Eh....
This is boring.
This was not good.
Oh, no.
I'm serious. I'm not saying no. I'm serious.
If you follow up after you've said no.
Oh, that's right.
I can follow up.
We can manage. It's important, right? Follow-up is the most important thing.
It's the most important thing.
Are you worried?
Yes, I do. Everyone tells you that.
Next, let's move on to the "decisive bumping".
This one is for the two of us,
Liz must say this.
Mayukan must say this. Mayukan must say this.
This person has to say this.
It's like they've decided on their own.
I'll go first.
I'll go this way.
This way.
One.
There's one.
You're a big fool, aren't you?
That's great.
I'm sorry, but you have the same name and the same color as "1".
It's bad, isn't it?
You've got it backwards!
If I let this girl in, she won't like me.
What?
That's not good.
She's depressed.
Yeah, she's pretty down too.
He's in a very bad mood.
Shall we go one more time?
I'm in.
Can we do it again?
Come on!
One.
To be honest, I think I'm prettier.
Two.
But this is easy to say
2 gets mad.
You mean like you just said?
I think 1 is good.
One sounds like something.
It's not good, but it's okay.
I think it's good.
It's not bad.
But two is...
But isn't it appropriate to expand two of them and make them look like a little something?
Yuusaka didn't think it was cute.
The members went in on it.A member of the group plugged in.
So what can you do?
No, that's why the members can do it.
That's why Yuka-chan...
You're me.
No, I think I'm prettier.
It's just...
It's you.
You can do it.
But this is good... it's definitely easier.
I'll do my best.
I'll do it then.
Okay.
Yes, sir.
Here.
Weird nicknames
A nickname.
Not "Yuuka-chan".
If you prefer Naochan...
It's so easy!
This is easy.
What?
Because number two...
The flower girl wants Naochan!
That's all you can talk about!
But that's pretty lousy.
If Yuka gets Naochan...
And Daddy gets Yuka...
And Daddy is Yuka...
Ai's terrible!
Ai no ko
I have to make it Papa's fault
Last but not least...
This way, please.
Oh!
Oh, I knew you'd do it.
I'll make sure he does the sliding negs.
Director.
Wow.
I'll make him do it.
It's bad to make him do it.
It's bad, it's bad, it's bad.
That's why
I mean, Ayala can do it.
And have them copy it.
I did the one where I slip.
But it's easier than you.
That's great.
It's easy.
It's the hardest.
You're probably the hardest.
You're the worst junior.
Do you want to reveal it?
I don't.
Oh, no.
I will.
I'll do it.
I won't.
That's not good.
Are you sure you want to go?
Let's go for it.
Okay, then.
May I play?
Yes, sir.
Hey!
English
(in kendo, noh, kyogen, etc.)
ei
English
pounding
Good luck!
I'm off
I'm off!
Nice to meet you!
You're so cute!
It's hard work.
Not at all.
He's eating something.
Really? You're rehearsing now?
Now.
Good morning.
Good morning!
I'm looking forward to it.
Dressed like this?
What? It's so hot.
I'm totally cool.
That's a nice way of putting it.
I really couldn't do that if I were you.
I wouldn't want people to hate me.
I'm a fan of Amefura myself.
I think it's a valuable experience to have you do this for me.
I'd like to tell you that I'm enjoying it.
I'd like to let you all know that I'm enjoying it.I think I'll let you all know.
I'm not talking about Yuzuki-chan, but Nao-chan. Isn't that pretty great?
This is great.
So, when this comes, I'm going to make it easy for you to understand, and I'm going to be a little grumpy.
It hurts my heart. It really hurts my heart. Good luck, Amefura.
Here you go, Amefura.
Sei-no-ichi.
You're too uncoordinated.
Okay, so...
I'm Yuzuki!
Yes! I am a big black lover of tension!
I'm looking forward to working with you!
Big black, big white, Yuzuki.
It's called "big white"!
You call it "big white"?
We usually say it the other way around.